風雨飄搖，黑暗環繞
In the rain or in the dark
我卻總是看得到希望
I will never lose the spark
就是它帶我度過低潮
that keeps me going when I'm low
大家都問我如何做到
Everybody asks me how
才能撐過這麼多難關
I get by when I get down
黑暗沒有那麼可怕
It's easy to get through the darkness
只要你知道
once you know
我可以教你怎樣
I can show you the way
能讓日子過得更明亮
to have a brighter day
你只要保持微笑
It only takes a smile
做什麼都有意義
to make it all worthwhile
我們能戰勝恐懼，
We can conquer our fears,
只要你保持笑容
laugh until happy tears
喜極而泣不難
fall to the ground
如果你害怕擔心，
If you're lost and afraid
覺得樂極就生悲
all the good times will fade
就追隨那聲音
just follow the sound
追隨那歡笑聲
Follow the sound of laughter
無人能擋，看向前方
Pulling through, standing tall
我們能克服一切阻礙
We can rise above it all
只要有朋友們在身旁
with our friends by our side
用笑臉面對危險
Face the danger with a grin
沒有什麼能贏過我們
'Cause there's no battle we can't win
我們永遠不會輸，永不分開
We will never fall, never divide
我們總會找到辦法
We will find the way
來面對新的明天
to face another day
你只要保持微笑
It only takes one smile
做什麼都有意義
to make it all worthwhile
我們能戰勝恐懼，
We can conquer our fears,
只要你保持笑容
laugh until happy tears
喜極而泣不難
fall to the ground
如果你害怕擔心，
If you're lost and afraid
覺得樂極就生悲
all the good times will fade
就追隨那聲音
just follow the sound
追隨那歡笑聲
Follow the sound of laughter
歡笑聲
of laughter
張開雙眼，就能看到答案
When you look inside, you'll find the answer
用心感受，就絕對不會錯
Coming from the heart you can't go wrong
露出笑容，就能找到歡笑
Do it with a smile and you'll find Laughter
找到你自己的旋律...
Find your melody and sing...
YEAH!
我們會戰勝恐懼，
We will conquer our fears,
只要你保持笑容
laugh until happy tears
喜極而泣不難
fall to the ground
有你們這群朋友，
With the friends that we've made
我們不會迷失方向
I know we'll never stray
只要追隨那聲音
if we follow the sound
追隨那歡笑聲
Follow the sound of laughter
噢，歡笑聲
Oh, laughter